export const questionData = [
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 1,
    question: "bell ",
    degree: "easy",
    trueAnswer: "zil",
    answer: ["Cevap", "Hava", "zil", "Sanat"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 2,
    degree: "easy",
    question: "beside ",
    trueAnswer: "yanında",
    answer: ["Etmek", "yanında", "inanmak", "Kesin"],
  },

  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 3,
    degree: "easy",
    question: "blood  ",
    trueAnswer: "kan",
    answer: ["Edinmek", "Fiil", "kan", "Boya "],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 4,
    degree: "easy",
    question: "carry  ",
    trueAnswer: "taşımak",
    answer: ["Aykırı", "kan", "Ilave", "taşımak"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 5,
    degree: "easy",
    question: "chance  ",
    trueAnswer: "şans",
    answer: ["Macera", "yeniden", "şans", "Avukat"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 6,
    degree: "medium",
    question: "A rabbit is _____ than a tortoise.  ",
    trueAnswer: "faster",
    answer: ["slower", "faster", "hotter", "colder"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 7,
    degree: "medium",
    question: "Making a cake is ____ making baklava.  ",
    trueAnswer: "not as difficult as    ",
    answer: [
      "more difficult than  ",
      "as difficult as  ",
      "not as difficult as",
      "as easy as",
    ],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 8,
    degree: "medium",
    question: "In my free time, I mostly ______ a song  ",
    trueAnswer: "listen to",
    answer: ["listen to", "speak to", " read", "write"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 9,
    degree: "medium",
    question: "____ can swim, but they can’t fly  ",
    trueAnswer: "Dogs",
    answer: ["Birds", "Dogs", "Planes", "doctor"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 10,
    degree: "medium",
    question: "John is an ____.  ",
    trueAnswer: "engineer",
    answer: ["engineer", "doctor", "teacher", "designer"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 11,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "For the project to...........our organisations need to trust each other completely and work in harmony.     ",
    trueAnswer: "succeed",
    answer: ["assess", "compile", "succeed", "attain"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 12,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "Angela runs her profitable wooden toy business from a...........ordinary cottage in a small village.  ",
    trueAnswer: "seemingly",
    answer: ["smartly", "movingly", "briefly", "seemingly"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 13,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "My brother isn’t very fit at the moment because he only exercises...........and hasn’t got a fitness routine.   ",
    trueAnswer: "irregularly",
    answer: ["intensely", "irregularly", "formerly", "initially"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 14,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "Roald Dahl used to work on his children's stories in a hut at the bottom of his garden where he could get completely...........in his writing.   ",
    trueAnswer: "absorbed",
    answer: ["absorbed", "accustomed", "compared", "associated"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 15,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "The teacher needn’t have criticised his essay so...........; after all, he is  foreign student and still has a slight problem expressing his thoughts properly.    ",
    trueAnswer: "harshly",
    answer: ["applicably", "unevenly", "harshly", "deliberately"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 16,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "Due to Argentina’s .......... economy, many people are choosing to grow their own vegetables to survive.   ",
    trueAnswer: "ailing",
    answer: ["bustling", "growing", "booming", "ailing"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 17,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "The River Elbe.........through eastern Germany and through Hamburg before reaching the North Sea. ",
    trueAnswer: "flows",
    answer: ["floats", "sinks", "flows", "drives"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 18,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "The teacher needn’t have criticised his essay so...........; after all, he is  foreign student and still has a slight problem expressing his thoughts properly.    ",
    trueAnswer: "harshly",
    answer: ["applicably", "unevenly", "harshly", "deliberately"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 19,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "Since the bombing of a nightclub in Bali, American, British and Australian officials have been gathering ......... on the activities of outlawed terrorist groups in Indonesia.  ",
    trueAnswer: "intelligence    ",
    answer: ["intelligence", "acknowledgement", "identification", "procedure"],
  },
  {
    userId: 1,
    id: 20,
    degree: "hard",
    question:
      "Tim’s wife, Sue, .......... that formal education for the very young hinders their progress and she is determined to teach her children at home for the first few years.",
    trueAnswer: "asserts",
    answer: ["predicts", "contradicts", "asserts", "intends"],
  },
];
